{
    "id": "c5ee5d992b22481081d44b3a69941e7b",
    "title": "Short answers exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2ae6d578681e4c748ee7e63a8183cdec",
            "title": "Short Answers Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "‘Have you got a light?’ ‘Yes, ………………………………….’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I have",
                        "I've"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Do you know the answer?’ ‘No, …………………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I do not",
                        "I don't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Will you give me a hand?’ ‘Yes, ……………………….’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I will",
                        "I'll"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Can you help me with the homework?’ ‘No, ………………………’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I cannot",
                        "I can't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Can I borrow your car?’ ‘No, …………………………….’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you cannot",
                        "you can't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Was the film interesting?’ ‘Yes, …………………………’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "it was",
                        "it's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Does she like flowers?’ ‘Yes, …………………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she does",
                        "she's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Can I use your computer?’ ‘Yes, ……………………….’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you can",
                        "you can't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Should we tell her?’ ‘No, ………………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "we shouldn't",
                        "we should not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Should I wait?’ ‘No, ………………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you shouldn't",
                        "you should not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}